Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
- No way.
- Yeah.
This is the Cuban spirit.
Dom! Dom!
Raldo. you said I...
You know I can't make a living
without my car.
It's not my problem. bro.
Dominic Toretto. I heard about you.
Welcome to my island.
Why you hooking up my cousin's car?
Cousin's car.
Not anymore.
He needed money.
I gave it to him.
He can't pay.
I take the car.
I-I just need a few more days.
"Few more days" wasn't part of the deal.
Come on.
You make a deal.
you gotta live up to it.
You make a deal...
you going to live up to it.
"Going to live up to it"?
Oh. so you one of those types.
You take everyone's ride
and then ship it back to the States?
You know what I respect?
Money.
You watch your mouth.
Now you got a problem.
I'm gonna keep it about the cars.
- You want a car. get it the right way.
- How?
Race for it.
I already own it. bro.
Not that car.
Mine.
Dom...
His-his car is the fastest car
on the island.
Do you know what he has under that hood?
He knows it doesn't matter
what's under a hood.
The only thing that matters
is who's behind the wheel.
You think so?
I know so.
Then race his car.
And we ain't racing
no quarter-mile here.
We race the Cuban mile.
Done.
Listen. I-I appreciate what
you're trying to do. but...
my car is the slowest car on the island.
Was.
Pull the seats. the doors. the battery.
If it ain't the motor. take it off.
Laughing gas?
Nah. Fed.
This is Cuban NOS.
You guys are crazy.
- What are you doing?
- Poor man's turbo.
Pull the vacuum line and hold on.
Old trick the Buster used to play.
in case of emergencies.
You know that's way too much boost
- for that engine.
- It's gonna be fast.
It's gonna be a bomb.
Only needs to go a mile.
That car belongs in the trash. bro.
Where are they going?
I don't know. Let's go.
Ghost him.
Sí.
Adios. Toretto.
Okay. Buster.
Let's see if this works.
That's impossible.
Look out!
Hold on. Hold on.
A deal's a deal.
You won my car.
And you earned my respect.
Keep your car.
Your respect is good enough for me.
Yo. cousin.
Sorry about your car.
Yours was too slow for a Toretto anyway.
Your Impala?
Are you serious?
Look at that smile.
I love it when you smile.
You make me happy.
Mmm. I think this place makes you happy.
It's like it speaks to you.
You remember that guy...
the racer and his dad?
The one with the boat engine
under the hood?
Yeah.
- Yeah.
- Of course.
I was... I was looking at them.
and I... and I couldn't help
but to imagine
what you'd be like if you were a dad.
No. no. no. no!
I'm not pregnant.
Is that what you want?
It's not about what I want
or what you want.
It's about why we haven't
asked the question.
And do you have enough faith
in the world?
I'll always ride for us.
Yeah. but would you ride for the world?
You hungry?
Mm-hmm.
- Same thing?
- Mm-hmm.
Two minutes.
What?
You need a hand?
Yeah. I think I do.
Thank you.
Sounds like you're not getting any fuel.
- Yeah?
- Probably the shutoff solenoid.
Let's see if we can get
some power to it.
What brings you to Cuba?
Same thing that brings
everyone else to Cuba.
Culture. people. beauty.
What brings you to Cuba?
Work.
Must be casual Friday.
How's that honeymoon going. Dom?
Your fuel relay is missing.
I know.
I love to play games...
beaten the best of 'em...
but I'm kind of in a rush.
so if you've got something
to say to me...
Oh. this is a very different game.
That I can assure you.
This...
There is something
much greater at work here.
This is fate.
I choose to make my own fate.
Not today.
Is this the road you take
to your apartment every morning?
What else is different. Dom?
Was Santiago's closed?
Did you have to
cross two blocks
to go get your Cuban coffees?
What is it. black. no sugar?
Yeah.
I put a lot of work
into getting you here today.
Well. now that I'm here.
what do you want?
I want you to work for me.
Work for you?
Oh. I could have saved you
a lot of time. then.
See. I don't work for anyone.
You can't walk away from this. Dom.
We're gonna have this conversation.
one way or the other.
You see. that's the funny thing
about fate.
It's cunning.
It can bring you beautiful things.
and it can also bring you
moments like this.
Oh. you're gonna want to work for me.
You're gonna betray your brothers.
abandon your code
and shatter your family.
You see. your team
is about to go up against
the only thing they can't handle.
And what's that?
You.
Oh. and. Dom.
I wouldn't mention this to anyone.
They are gonna be hitting us
with everything they got.
So we want to engage with maximum speed.
Neutralize their shooters.
and then move on to our objective.
There's two things
I want you to keep in mind.
Number one... I chose you
for this squad because you are
the most fearsome warriors
on the planet.
And number two... You go out there.
you do your job. and you take 'em down.
Everyone... and I mean everyone...
manis and pedis at the mall
later on today.
Huh?
One. two three!
Monarchs!
Yah!
What?
I don't want to play anymore.
All right. let's go. girls.
Let's go. let's go. let's go!
Final two minutes.
Quite the cheering section.
Oh. yeah.
Yeah. yeah. it's the moms.
they come out to support the kids.
Except there seem to be
more moms than kids.
Way more moms.
Yeah.
It's a big soccer town.
Let's go. girls!
So. your intel was spot-on.
That Damocles 7 EMP weapon
that went missing in the Gulf...
arms dealers from the Liberation Front
- have it in Berlin.
- Shit.
This thing can wipe out
an entire electrical grid
in a major city.
No lights. no power...
instant Stone Age.
Chloe. Maya. you can't let her
run by you like that.
- Let's go. let's go! Cross!
- Agent Hobbs.
this is a Class 4 WMD.
Do you have any idea
- what's at stake here?
- That's it. Go. go. go. go!
Yes. I know exactly
what is at stake here. okay?
If the Pink Butterflies
beat my Red Dragons. that means
we lose the championship...
which means I have
20 little girls who are crying.
and that's not a good thing.
Which then means I have to spend
a lot of time in ice cream shops
and spend a lot of time
at Tay Tay concerts.
Tay Tay?
Come... Taylor Swift.
Gotta be shittin' me.
Get it together. okay?
- Let's go. girls.
- Go. go. go!
We need you to do this.
It's a lot of lives at stake.
- All right. but I need to be clear here.
- Ah. ah!
The U.S. government cannot
sanction this operation in any way.
- You're on your own.
- Hey...
This thing goes sideways.
you don't just get burned.
you go to prison.
And there's nothing
we can do to get you out.
Let me tell you something.
The only thing that I love more
than saving lives
is my daughter.
So. if you don't shut up
with this government bullshit right now
and start showing some team spirit
and respect for the Red Dragons.
I'm gonna have all 20 of them line up
and kick you right in the tay-tay.
Go. Dragons.
Say it again.
- Go. Dragons!
- Attaboy.
Go. Dragons. Go. Dragons.
Go. She's open!
Go. go! Yes!
That is my daughter right there. Yes.
Yes. come here.
- How did I do?
- Awesome.
Nice job. kid.
Daddy's gotta go to work?
Uh. yeah.
Daddy's gotta go to work.
Now. you're gonna need
to get a team you can trust.
Oh. I already got one.
- Hey. Dom.
- Hey. Hobbs.
I got a job in Berlin.
and I need a favor. brother.
No problem. I'll grab the team
and meet you in Berlin.
Thanks. man.
I'll see you soon.
You were only supposed
to create a diversion. Roman.
That was a diversion!
How many of the damn explosives
did you use?
I don't know. Tej.
All of it?
- Wait. all of it?
- Roman. Jesus Christ.
You got more of your fan club ahead.
They're still on us.
These guys are taking this personal.
Roman. we just blew up their facility
and stole their EMP.
Other than your doctor's cold finger.
I'd say it's about
as personal as it can get.
Phase two.
Phase two? So. you just
gonna keep that to yourself?
What happened to phase one?
What about that part?
Yeah. Remember the airplane?
Everyone drove their cars out but you?
I told you my engine seized up.
It's your balls that seized up.
Just follow my lead. okay?
And. Roman. whatever you do...
don't think.
What?
Tej. drop it.
Bombs away.
Split now.
Holy...!
Great plan. Tej.
But just so you know. you missed some.
Oh. just wait for it.
Oh. shit!
I hate you. Tej!
Got your ass.
You good?
I'll see you when it's done.
All right. great job. team.
Let's break off.
and meet me at the safe house.
A hell of a job. brother.
When we get back to the base.
beer's on me.
You lost your goddamn mind. Toretto?
Toretto. you put hands on
that thing. you're gonna have
the whole world gunning
for you. including me.
I don't know what you're doing.
but you better think
about this. Toretto.
It ain't too late to stop this.
It is now.
That sumbitch just crossed us.
- What?
- Wait a second.
What are you talking about?
Dom took the EMP.
Bullshit.
Where are you?
It's too late for me.
Get out of here.
He wrecked my truck and he took it.
I saw that look in his eye.
and I've seen that look before.
Dominic Toretto just went rogue.
All right. I got
his phone records. y'all.
It's a whole bunch of calls
to untraceable numbers.
Burner phones. right?
Nah. Scrambler.
Same number. but they got some sort
of micro-router to bury the signal path.
which means Dom is clearly communicating
with somebody
that's above our pay grade.
Look. I don't know Dom as well as you.
but if we just look at the facts...
Dom's been having
highly encrypted conversations
with some mysterious person.
He took out Hobbs.
He stole an EMP.
Now he's disappeared.
So. what are you saying?
Maybe we should consider
the fact that Hobbs is right.
Dom did go rogue.
Letty.
We're all in this
trying to figure it out. okay?
We're on the side.
You sure about that. Roman?
Before you judge the man.
remember. you're breathing right now
because he saved your life.
You just gonna let her
bump your shoulder like that?
I'm-I'm just saying. that...
that was a little aggressive.
What you gonna do. e-mail her?
Check.
Moment. will you. fellas?
Thank you.
Well. this is an exciting new look.
It's a little tight
in the crotch. as always.
What boy-band bus did she fall out of?
It's my new junior associate.
He's working with me on this.
- All yours.
- Agent Hobbs.
Mr. Nobody and I have
been given the authority
to get you out of this.
All you have to do is agree
to the terms. and you're free.
What's Training Wheels
talking about? What terms?
Confess to your crimes in Berlin.
Treason. international espionage.
massive destruction of civic property.
You do that. we close the case.
- And?
- And the DSS blacklists you.
- Germany loves that.
- Officially.
- you will be a criminal.
- Wait. Whoa. whoa. whoa.
You need to work
on your delivery. all right?
Unofficially...
you're off the books.
You come work with me.
I'm not a criminal.
Luke. come on. Labels.
There is no confession.
There are no backroom deals.
Got myself into this.
I'm gonna get myself out of it.
- You know that.
- I do. and that's what I told him.
Well. there you have it.
Good luck in the courts. man.
What about your daughter?
You know. if you're not
gonna do it for your country.
at least do it for your kid.
Big mistake. kid.
Hold on. Look. Luke.
He's still working from the manual.
I mean. he doesn't even
really know the rules.
Now. come on. give him a break.
Give me a break.
Luke.
Appreciate it.
It's good to see you. Nobody.
You. too.
Rule number one...
Know your audience.
I gave you your shot.
You shit the bed.
Now I'm gonna show you
how to get this done.
You're mine now. copper!
Yeah. that badge don't go far in here!
You're dead. cop. Dead!
I'm gonna slice
some bacon off your back. pig!
Well. well. well.
Luke Hobbs behind bars.
Would you look at that.
The bent cop got his day.
You know. that color looks good on you.
Yeah. it'd look a whole hell
of a lot better with your blood on it.
Yeah. good luck with that. Hercules.
Lawman gone bad. huh?
Such a cliché.
Oh. well. welcome to the club.
I wouldn't get that twisted. son.
We ain't in no club.
We got nothing in common.
And unlike you.
I ain't gonna be here long.
So why don't you get
your candy-ass back out there
and toss some more salads. boy.
What. you bring a shovel. did you?
Because it's 38 feet
of steel and concrete.
Or so I've been told.
Better get to digging.
You wanker.
Yeah.
Move.
Say that again.
If I say it again.
it'll be to a corpse.
I'm going to enjoy this.
Welcome back. Dom.
Nice job out there.
You excited about tonight?
You're going on this?
You're with me. Dom.
I am impressed.
That job went down
exactly like we planned.
It is something to watch somebody
at the top of their game.
It must've been a real thrill
from 30.000 feet.
Oh. come on. there has to be
a small part in you
that enjoyed what you just did
back there.
No? Hmm?
Showing me your shoe collection?
Yep.
A pair for every occasion.
You have enough guns in here
to outfit a small army. huh?
This? Oh. this is just
the tip of the iceberg.
You know what I like about you. Dom?
You're a genuine outlaw.
I mean. you're a man
who lives by his own rules.
Which is surprising because.
when I saw you in Cuba.
I heard about a guy
who almost killed you with a motorcycle.
and you let him keep his car?
Oh. that confused you?
Hmm.
Of course I could have taken his car.
Of course I could have beaten him down.
But it's about something bigger.
This way...
I changed him.
That's not your responsibility.
But it's who I am.
Let me ask you something. Dom.
What's the best thing in your life?
Family.
No. it's not.
Not if you're being honest.
It's the ten seconds
between start and finish
when you're not thinking about anything.
No family.
No obligations.
Just you...
that engine...
that open road...
being free.
I gotta tell you.
this whole saving-the-world.
Robin Hood nonsense
you've been doing recently...
it's bullshit.
It's not you.
Be who you are.
Why live only a quarter mile at a time
when you can live
your whole life that way?
Is that it?
Is that all those bloated-out
muscles will give you?
All show and no go.
Oh. I got plenty of go.
Yeah?
You must have misplaced that
when I kicked your arse up
and down that office of yours.
Yeah.
Just like you Brits...
rewriting history. huh?
All I know is it wasn't me
that was thrown out
of a four-story window.
Jumped.
I jumped out of a four-story window
saving my partner's life.
'Cause where I'm from.
we don't settle fights
by throwing bombs.
Well. that's funny.
because where I'm from.
we don't need women
to run to our rescue.
I mean. do you really believe
you can stand in front of me
and beat me in a straight-up.
old-fashioned fistfight?
Let me tell you something.
Me and you. one on one.
no one else around...
I will beat your ass
like a Cherokee drum.
Maybe one day we'll find out.
Oh. you better hope
that day never comes.
I said no. Mr. Nobody.
I'm not leaving this cell.
I'll get out my way.
The right way!
Hey! Why is the door open?
Get back in your cell!
Relax.
It's just a malfunction.
- Get back!
- Just a malfunction.
♪ Got the whole spot
going up like that ♪
♪ Laid back hot in the cut like that ♪
♪ Speakerbox blast... ♪
Stop him!
Don't let him get away!
♪ In fact. we about to go up like that ♪
♪ Speakerbox. speakerbox blast ♪
♪ Blast. blast. blast.
blast. blast. blast ♪
♪ We can switch it up like that ♪
♪ Speakerbox blast.
speaker-speakerbox blast. go ♪
♪ Back in the back
in the cut like that ♪
♪ Speakerbox blast.
speaker-speakerbox blast. go ♪
♪ Speakerbox blast. go rat-a-tat-tat ♪
♪ In fact. we about to go up like ♪
♪ Got the whole spot ♪
♪ Going up ♪
♪ Got the whole spot going ♪
I've been waiting a long time for this.
Keep waiting. bitch.
Rubber bullets.
Big mistake.
♪ We can switch it up
like that. that. that. that ♪
♪ Like blast ♪
♪ We about to go up like ♪
Well. that took longer than I expected.
- Two questions.
- Yeah.
- My daughter?
- With your sister.
Toretto?
It's interesting you ask.
This is my new base.
Welcome to nowhere.
It's a little sterile for you.
Listen. there's something
I want to talk to you about after.
Hey. listen. guys. thanks...
Whoa. whoa. whoa. what?
Handcuffs? What is this?
It's called abuse of power.
You told me to round them up.
I didn't tell you to hand...
Cut 'em loose. Oh. man.
This is embarrassing.
I'm sorry. guys. Really. I...
So. this is how you treat old friends?
Friends?
We don't even really know
- who the hell this guy is.
- Doesn't matter who I am. Tej.
- I'm. like. nobody. okay?
- Nobody. So. then. who is he?
Him? He's nothing.
He's. like. less than me.
Tej. trust me. brother.
that's a maze you don't want
to get lost in.
Clearly. we're getting nowhere
with nobody.
I've been in here for four hours.
and my ribs are showing.
I don't know about y'all. but I'm out.
- I wouldn't recommend that.
- What?
Well. thanks to your botched Berlin job.
you all made Interpol's
top ten most wanted list.
- Top ten.
- Mm-hmm.
That's all right.
Yeah. Well. uh... not you. Roman.
- What do you mean?
- You just missed the cut.
You're number 11. so...
- I... I missed? What are you...
- Yeah.
That's impossible.
What number did they come in at?
Six. eight. nine.
ten.
- She's ten?
- Mm-hmm.
She just got here. That's impossible.
There's no way she's a ten.
Oh. she's definitely a ten.
What?
How about we focus on someone
who we're not gonna find
on anybody's list.
We're awaiting hard confirmation.
but I believe that's the cyber terrorist
known as Cipher.
Wait. no.
Cipher's an organization.
not... not a person.
Not according to our sources.
- What does she want?
- No one knows.
Cipher is like a digital act of God.
They...
well. she can manipulate
world systems from the shadows...
governments. global markets.
Anything that can be hacked
is hers to play with.
And here's the kicker...
you'll never find her linked
to any of it.
Her digital identity is scrubbed
every few seconds worldwide.
Six years of
the intelligence community's
coordinated efforts
have turned up nothing
but this single photo.
So. basically. she's the bogeyman.
Damn. she's...
one of the hottest bogeymans
I've ever seen.
I mean. if y'all know her.
tell her to get at your boy.
- What are you. 12?
- That was my shin. mother...
Let's just say.
people are scared
of the hacker group Anonymous.
But even Anonymous won't mess with her.
What the hell does any of this
have to do with us?
Probably nothing. Letty.
but I do find it interesting
that. apparently. for some reason.
she's now working with this guy.
Do you know why?
Gee. no. Letty. I don't.
He's already delivered
a fully operational EMP into her hands.
Detonate that. they can turn
any city in the world into a war zone.
So. then. what is it
you're suggesting we do?
Maybe we find Dom. huh?
Well. first. let's catch him
and then figure out why he's turned.
And we put a stop to whatever
bullshit they got planned.
So. y'all want us to track Dom.
Yeah. I know. Roman.
it's kind of a big job.
It's impossible.
Which is why I'm bringing in
an extra pair of hands.
Ah. my day just got
a whole hell of a lot better.
Mr. Nobody. you want to tell me
why you just put me in a room with this
tea and crumpets eating.
criminal sumbitch?
What a big mouth on a small head.
coming from prisoner 6753.
Don't think we've forgotten
everything that you've done.
We are not teaming up with this guy.
Let's get one thing clear...
I ain't on your team.
I don't care about you.
your crew or your little family.
- I'm here for Cipher.
- What are you gonna do.
apply for a job?
Head asshole?
You know. I think that tight T-shirt's
cutting off the circulation
to your brain.
You should get a bigger size.
Cipher came to me first.
Wanted me to steal Nightshade for her.
When I said no.
she went after my brother.
Ah. yes. brother Owen.
Who could forget him. huh?
Former hell-raiser and current guest
at a nasty little black-site prison.
Cipher corrupted him
and left him for dead.
So. if I get a shot to take her down.
believe me. Flex. I'm taking it.
You're taking my boot right up your ass
- is what you're taking.
- Guys. guys. guys. guys.
The fastest way to find Cipher
is through Toretto.
Now. aside from myself. there's only
two men in the world
that have ever managed
to actually track him down
with any success.
And guess what... they're both
standing in front of me right now.
So. like it or not. you two
are gonna work together.
You got that?
I'm gonna take that as a yes.
Am I the only one seeing this?
Oh. this ought to be good.
Use God's Eye.
We put our lives on the line.
running around the world
trying to figure this thing out.
It can find anybody. right?
Let's use it to find Dom.
It's that easy. Done.
Roman. that is a great idea.
Did you hear that?
"Great idea"?
No. no. no. no. no. don't
tune it out. huh? Uh-huh. Huh.
See. you and this guy. right here.
Stay out of my lane. dude.
It's all me right here.
you know what I mean?
It's crazy.
Mr. Nobody. let's fire it up. huh?
Got him. He's in London.
Yeah.
Wait. We've got
a second match in Hong Kong.
Beijing and Seoul.
And Tokyo.
And just about every other major city
- on the planet.
- And so...
God's Eye was where we started.
But Cipher's already created
an evasion that masks their location
by pinging random spots
all over the globe.
but it was a good thought. Roman.
So. she's made my program obsolete.
And that. Ramsey. is why you're here.
See. simple solutions aren't
gonna cut it here. slick.
Why you look at me when you say that?
Wait a second.
Wait. wait. Simple solutions
might just cut it.
You see. in order for God's Eye
to give off all these false pings.
means they have to be
using a FLEA relay.
Watch these two.
Which means it has a decaying
sync randomizer.
Which we can reverse...
And track it back
to the originating source
and find Dom's true location.
I'm telling you.
they got skills.
That was my idea.
That's what I was saying.
- Remember in there?
- All right.
Let's try this.
It's working.
Time you want to check your manual
and start organizing a force response.
Let's get a hold
of our international assets...
He's still green.
Yeah. like fresh baby shit.
Soon as we have Toretto's
location. I want to mobilize.
Let's get a hold of a better asshole.
Uh. no one respects you. uh...
- Cover.
- Get away from me.
No problem. Bad breath.
Mm...
All right. they're not in China.
Or Russia.
Europe's clear.
But this one's not going away.
This is interesting.
Why?
Because that's here.
Pull up all security monitors
on this building. now.
Surprise.
Did you all enjoy that?
Next-generation concussion grenade.
It scrambles your senses.
Don't worry.
it will wear off in an hour.
Probably.
Hello. Deckard.
Nice to see you again.
Look at this.
Body's not even cold. Dom.
Your family's already replacing you.
You chose the losing team.
I guess your brother
is smarter than you.
Smart move embedding God's Eye
into the mainframe.
Irritating to make me have to
come all the way
down here to get it. but...
Let's go.
Dom!
You gonna turn your back on family?
Just like that?
Let's go.
You okay?
That wasn't him.
I don't know what she's got on him.
but that wasn't Dom.
Brian would know what to do.
No!
We can't bring Brian and Mia into this.
We agreed on that.
I know.
You saved me.
I'm... I'm not really sure
how to thank you.
No need.
You got a computer I can use?
That I do.
Psst. yo.
What. man?
You see this?
Like. they really
going at it over there.
Must be the accent.
Bro...
he ain't got no accent to her.
They're from the same place.
- Uh. yeah. I was... I was just joking.
- Yeah. okay.
I got the accent. Exotic.
Exotic?
Barstow?
Ghetto?
Barstow is exotic to her.
Back there. was that for her.
for me or you?
And was it even necessary?
Necessary?
Nothing is necessary.
Everything is a choice.
And I simply made one. but so did you.
You could have stopped me.
but you chose not to.
Wonder what Letty thought about that.
The problem with putting
your foot on a tiger's neck
is you can never let it up.
I think I need to remind you
why you chose to be here.
Elena.
Dom.
I'm sorry.
You shouldn't have come.
Nothing could have kept me away.
Now she has the three of us.
Do you want to see him?
See Papa?
Yeah. Yeah.
Come and see Papa.
Papa.
When I realized I was pregnant.
you had just found out Letty was alive.
So I decided. when Letty and you
got back from your honeymoon.
I was going to tell you.
And then she took us
before I had the chance.
His name?
I call him Marcos.
But that's his middle name.
I thought his father
should give him his first name.
I'm sorry. Dom.
There's nothing to be sorry for.
Whatever happens...
...just save our son.
Your son.
Good visit?
I know.
I know what you're thinking.
I just let the guards go.
so there's only two opponents
in the room.
Rhodes has the gun.
so you'll take him out first.
I know you.
You have the will
so you'll find the way.
Once you've got it. you'll take him out.
Maybe even me.
And then you're thinking...
Elena's a cop.
Maybe the two of you
can fight your way out of here.
It's so much to think about.
Let me make it easier for you.
Do with it as you wish.
Have you heard of choice theory. Dom?
There is a bunch of axioms.
but only two you really need
to concern yourself with.
One... The only person's behavior
we can control is our own.
And two... The only thing we can truly
give another person is information.
So let me give you some.
You see these cameras in here?
The moment you make a move.
highly paid men with weapons
will make their way into this room
with one very specific instruction.
It's not to save me.
It's to kill your son.
Now. that's a lot of bullets.
and it only takes one
for you to lose everything.
So I have to ask you because...
I know family is so important to you.
Is that really a choice
you want to make?
Because I'm ready if you are.
If I pull this trigger...
and God knows I want to...
if I killed everyone on this plane.
I still couldn't get in there.
'Cause of your two-man fail-safe system.
Since I'm alone!
I got no choice!
I didn't think so.
You want to see the old Dom?
Watch.
Bitch.
- Don't... don't...
- Sweet dreams.
Please!
Damn it.
She wiped it all.
Took God's Eye.
That was the one thing
we could use to find them.
We lost everything.
What you got. princess?
Finding Toretto.
But I got a couple of minutes to spare.
if you want me to send you
to the hospital... again.
Yo. Rules.
- First off. that's not my name.
- Little Nobody.
- Don't call me that.
- Oh. that's definitely sticking.
Great. Do me a favor and tell
Your Majesty over there
that we're gonna find Toretto.
We find Toretto together as a team.
And when all this is said and
done. I'll be happy to slap
that dick garage right off his face.
Wait a minute. guys.
I think Deckard's
actually onto something.
How do you think Dom and Cipher
got into the country without us knowing?
Ghost flights.
I thought untraceable aircraft was all
- Internet conspiracy stuff.
- It's not.
Satellites and radar grids
all across the globe
shift like an ocean.
And they've got channels
that open and close.
And theoretically.
if you know the right people
who know the right patterns...
You can fly
right through the blind spots
completely undetected.
So. you know where Dom is headed?
Yeah. New York.
You see there. Luke?
What did I tell you?
You guys are gonna get along just great.
Which proves rule number two...
you never lose everything.
Fire up the chopper.
Well. guys. have a ball
in the Big Apple.
♪ I'm with the gang. gang. gang ♪
♪ And we 'bout to go up ♪
♪ Switching lanes. it's a thang
every time we show up ♪
♪ You lame. lame. lame.
and you so below us ♪
♪ Bet your ho she know us ♪
♪ 'Cause you know we blowed up ♪
♪ We stay down... ♪
And why are we
traveling like this again?
Because Dom took God's Eye.
So we need to stay off the grid.
But like this?
Look here. man.
Before I throw up in my mouth.
let me ask you...
what are we doing here?
That's a good question. Roman.
Let me show you.
Welcome to our new base of operations.
No. seriously. what is this place?
This...
is heaven.
It's the agency garage.
They call it the Toy Shop.
This is where we house every vehicle
seized from drug dealers
on the East Coast.
Now. Mr. Nobody said.
"If we're gonna have a chance
at catching Dom...
...we're gonna have to be damn fast."
Figured this would help.
You got anything American?
What's the matter with you. huh?
Miss America.
What. are you allergic to quality?
This is the most durable
British vehicle ever built.
Oops.
I peed in your tea.
You're gonna fix that.
We got a tank.
750-horsepower.
6.6-liter V-8 Duramax engine
with an M153 CROWS
remotely operated
weapons station on top.
You didn't get this from drug dealers.
No. No. that. uh...
that. the United States Army lent me.
It's a Ripsaw unmanned combat vehicle.
Did you hear something?
See. the Army's developing
machines like this
that soldiers can drive from a mile away
so they can stay safe and alive.
But luckily.
there's a backup driver's seat
for those of us that like
to get more... hands-on.
I'm sitting there wondering
this whole time...
Oh. whoa.
...will this thing feel like valet
- at Cheesecake Factory.
- Whoa.
No one is getting hands-on.
She doesn't go on city streets.
Wow.
I'm in love.
Again...
no. no.
That's a million-dollar show car.
The point is to not draw attention.
It's reverse psychology.
Dom will never see it coming.
It's neon orange.
The International Space Station
would see it coming.
Go choose anything less conspicuous.
No. no. no. Calipers are my...
This is ridiculous.
- Not happening.
- Hey. my man.
you can put that down right there.
This is a gift. a real gift.
I know what you're doing.
I like your beard.
You're Blanta.
Black Santa?
No. I'm serious.
Put it down right there.
What are you doing?
Engine's misfiring.
I gotta check it out.
No. that's not part of the plan. Dom.
Clearly.
But unless you want the engine
to seize on the job...
You have five minutes.
I want another visual.
I got an ATM.
I don't like this.
I want to see Toretto.
- There are no more cameras.
- Then find something.
Punch in on something reflective.
A car mirror. anything.
Do you know who I am?
It's why I'm here.
Do you know what I'm capable of?
I'll give you until I finish me cuppa.
And I'm fucking thirsty.
I've got limited time.
so I won't take up too much of yours.
Oh. no.
No. you've already taken
everything I have of value. Mr. Toretto.
What more could you possibly want?
To give you something back.
Talk to me.
Something is not right here.
First time I saw my son
was behind a bulletproof glass.
When he heard my voice...
...I could see in his eyes
he knew I was his father.
When he reached for me.
I couldn't hold him.
It's the worst pain I ever felt.
I know you know exactly how that feels.
Maybe we could change that.
And. now. why do I think
you're about to suggest
something really dodgy. Mr. Toretto?
It's why I'm here.
Jesus. punch in on something.
I'm not liking this.
Something's not right.
Rhodes. you close?
Yeah.
Go.
The delivery truck's moving.
"Captain Deckard Shaw.
"Distinguished himself
by acts of gallantry
"at the risk of his life above
and beyond the call of duty.
"His bold actions saved the lives
"of hostages and his teammates.
Recommendation... the Victoria Cross."
The highest honor the British
government has ever given...
to a traitor.
Something about
this whole thing that just
doesn't add up to me.
Well. that would be
the same kind of funny math
that says a DSS agent
who has a Silver Star for valor
stole an EMP.
Sound familiar. huh?
You want to give me a hand?
- On three?
- Yeah.
One. two. three.
You know what. Twinkle Toes?
In another life. I bet me and you
could have done some serious damage.
- Yeah. we could've.
- Yeah.
Shame I'm gonna have to bounce your head
off the fender when this is all over.
Ah. well. with all due respect. Captain.
when this whole thing is over.
we're gonna find a location.
and I'm gonna knock your teeth
so far down your throat.
you're gonna stick a toothbrush
right up your ass to brush 'em.
Get me God's Eye.
God's Eye active.
Good.
Let's find us a Russian.
I spy with my little eye
a Minister of Defense.
Upload those coordinates to Dom's nav.
Copy that.
He's in the third car.
It's a Guard Class limousine.
Where's my team?
- Where's his team?
- There's no sign of them yet.
They're off the grid.
They're probably just
bunkered down somewhere.
I'm closing in on 'em.
You guys ready?
One thing I can guarantee. Dom...
no one's ready for this.
I want every chip
with a zero-day exploit
in a two-mile radius
around that motorcade now.
There's over a thousand of them.
Hack 'em all.
It's zombie time.
I'd buckle up if I were you.
Safety sensors overridden.
Thank you.
Whoa. whoa!
Hey!
Target the motorcade.
And here they come.
Ouch.
Police escort down.
Take out the lead and follow cars.
Two more down.
They're still under warranty.
We got an army of cars
driving themselves!
Send backup! Send SWAT!
I don't care if you send
the goddamn Boy Scouts!
Just send them some help!
Now. that's Dom.
The motorcade just turned on Seventh.
Perfect. Make it rain.
Target immobilized.
You're up. Dom.
Give me the case.
Good work. Dom.
Meet you at the pickup.
I think I know where my team's at.
Where?
Right in front of me.
This is on you.
Get out of there. Dom.
Guys. I know why Dom's here.
Police scanners are saying
he stole a nuclear football.
It's over. Toretto.
Get your ass out of the car now.
So. that's how you want to play this?
Let's play.
Don't do this. Dom.
He's going for it.
- What are you doing?
- It's a trap.
Damn it!
Now I know what it feels like
to be every cop ever chasing us.
I'm gonna get a little closer.
I'm gonna pit him.
Oh. so you just gonna pit Dom?
Little Nobody has clearly lost
his little mind.
I'm on him.
Easy. Work together.
- Look out!
- Wait. wait. wait!
Oh. sh...
I'll take the shortcut.
Look out! Watch those people!
Big Sexy coming through!
Not this time. Dom.
Watch the drag. or the line will snap!
Stretch him out. Hold him.
He's gotta have about
2.000 horsepower in that thing.
Try 3.000.
Try five.
Get out of there.
I'm working on it.
Stop working on it. and do it.
No. no. no. no.
This is my Bentley!
No! No!
Get that case and run.
Move.
They thought this was
gonna be a street fight.
What are you waiting for. Toretto?
No!
Let's get out of here!
Letty. stop!
What are you gonna do?
I don't know why you're doing this.
but I know one thing...
You love me.
And you are not gonna shoot me.
You should have given him the case.
'cause I won't chase you.
Okay.
I will just take it from a dead girl.
You willing to die for it?
Let's go. then.
Anything?
They're gone.
And DOD confirmed
it was a nuclear football.
He's got an EMP
and nuclear launch codes.
I don't know what it is.
but... but they're building
towards something.
Deckard?
He didn't make it.
I'm disappointed in you. Dom.
When push came to shove.
you were gonna let Letty
just walk away with the codes.
- You got the codes!
- Rhodes got the codes.
You made the choice to let her go.
And now I have to make one of my own.
They are adorable
little things. aren't they?
God. I hope I don't hurt him.
They're just designed to be so cute.
Look. psychotic. I did exactly
what you asked me to do.
Don't do this.
This is your doing.
My doing?!
Da-da-da.
Dada. Dada.
Please don't hurt him. I'm begging you.
I don't want you to beg.
I want you to learn.
Learn what?!
Everyone knows family
is the most important thing
in your life. so...
...I understand
why you did what you did.
I really do.
Dada.
But it was the wrong choice.
This is the consequence of that.
No. No! No!
Wait. wait. wait. wait.
W-Wait.
- Save your son!
- No!
No!
Shh...
Can you pull up the footage
from the guy in the alley?
Traffic cams.
I got you.
I knew it.
I recognize that guy.
That's Connor Rhodes.
I met him when I was working
with Shaw's brother.
He wanted us to get
the Nightshade device for him.
He must've been working
with that bitch the whole time.
Connor Rhodes.
He's also linked
to somebody I'd quite like to forget.
Mose Jakande.
Warlord who tried to get God's Eye.
Which means that's twice that Dom
has messed up Cipher's business.
Everything you're feeling right now...
this rage. this sense of loss...
it's not real.
It's an adaptive. evolutionary response.
It's a survival instinct
wired deep into our brains to ensure
continuation of the species.
When early man
would visit a watering hole.
if they didn't watch their child
and it got snatched by a crocodile...
...our brains would create a painful
but instructional memory
so it would never happen again.
This idea of family
that is so core with you.
that rules your world.
it's a biological lie.
You don't have to accept it.
I don't.
Did you really think you could destroy
two of my teams
without any repercussions?
I wouldn't have even looked your way
if you hadn't done that.
You didn't even know you had a kid.
You can thank me for that
and start doing the job
I'm asking you to do.
Help you start a war.
Is that what you think I want?
That's so limited.
I didn't take that football
to start a war
any more than I took your son
to start a family.
Taking your son got me the codes.
The codes will get me the nukes.
and the nukes will get me what I want
today. tomorrow
and every day after that.
And what's that?
Accountability.
The second I fire off
one of those nukes.
I put the superpowers
of this world on notice
that when they cross the line.
I'm gonna be there
to hold them responsible.
Because the truth is. Dom.
to the world out there...
...I am the crocodile
at the watering hole.
We've got one last job to do.
I have known one thing
about you. Cipher.
Behind those contacts.
your eyes are brown.
Beneath that dye. your hair is black.
There was probably beauty
inside you once.
but somehow you let it all die away.
You're so wrapped up in being a mystery.
you don't know who
the hell you are anymore.
You're lost...
you're alone...
and you're scared.
If I were you. I'd kiss my son.
Because. whether you value it or not.
all of this...
your plane. your security and you...
are still on this Earth because of him.
The problem we've had
with tracking Cipher
is there's nothing to trace.
But now we have Rhodes' information.
And we're getting snapshots of his data
before it's scrubbed off the Net.
That look like somebody's bank account.
so why don't we just go ahead...
It's a longitude.
Given the fact that Dom
hit a Russian motorcade.
safe to say it's Russia.
Go ahead and bring up the map.
Good. Let's start here
and run the possibilities.
Yalta. Poltava...
It's like they just
threw letters together.
- Kronyurt...
- It's Vladovin.
What are you doing here?
What?
Told you I was gonna
check in on you from time to time
to see how you were doing.
By the way. not so hot.
But there's nothing in Vladovin.
- It's just ice.
- That's funny.
Could've sworn there was
a secret Russian naval base
where they retrofitted
Cold War submarines.
Well. technically.
it's not Russian anymore.
Base was taken over by a terror group
of military separatists
about a month ago.
and the Russians
haven't taken it back yet.
so there is a little window
of opportunity here.
Russian submarines.
Nuclear football.
It sounds like. everything we do.
our legs gonna be blown off.
It sounds like you still
number 11 on the list.
It sounds like you've changed
since your little
punk-ass facial hairs done came in.
Like a fake-ass Barry White looking...
Guys. guys.
Hey. we gotta call this in.
All the way up the chain.
That's good thinking. champ.
except. unfortunately.
the Russian Minister of Defense
got himself involved
in a little incident
on U.S. territory and...
two governments aren't talking
to each other for a while.
By the time they do. it'll be too late.
So. any other suggestions?
Yeah.
I got one.
How about we just stop 'em ourselves?
You're talking about
a Russian military base.
- Separatist.
- Whatever. It's suicide.
It's stopping World War Three.
What's it gonna be. rook?
You gonna close your eyes
on this one. too?
Pray that the apocalypse
doesn't come knocking
on your mama's front door?
Or you gonna saddle up. be a man
and save the entire goddamn world?
You know. I think I figured it out.
What's that?
Rule number three.
Which is?
There are no rules.
What'd I tell you. Luke?
I knew he'd get it in three.
Aerial transport leaves in an hour.
Take whatever vehicle you want.
All bets are off.
- All bets are off?
- Bets are off?
Letty. I don't like
telling you this one bit.
but the game's changed.
Before. we were just trying
to catch Dom.
but now. after all this.
I want you to know. if I have to.
I'm gonna put him down.
Then you might have
to take us both down.
I'm freezing. man.
This ain't for me.
I come from a different kind
of lifestyle. brah.
Ladies know me.
They know where I'm at with it.
I tried to take a piss...
I didn't even recognize myself.
Man. that's entirely
too much information.
I'm just saying.
Well. one thing's for sure.
Dom's gotta be either working
with them or making a trade.
because no one would be this insane
to hit this place without a damn army.
I wouldn't be so sure about that.
Speak of the devil.
All right. Dom. you're one step closer
to that family reunion.
400 meters to base.
Prep the EMP.
Let's take these defenses down.
Gates are open.
Let's get this party started.
EMP is recharging.
- How long?
- 60 seconds.
All right. Dom. you have
one pulse left in that EMP.
That sub is heavily insulated.
You're gonna need
to be right underneath it
for this thing to work.
Come on.
Yes!
Two birds with one stone.
We've got control of the sub.
Dom. we are good.
Head over to the rendezvous.
Okay. Matty...
let's take this baby for a spin.
Damn.
I think Cipher just rebooted that sub
to slave its command system.
What the hell is he talking about?
In layman's terms.
she just carjacked a submarine.
We can't let it get away.
There's the control room.
If you can get me into that wheelhouse.
I can tap the network
and counter-hack Cipher.
Keep it from lowering into the water.
No. what we need to do
is get me on that sub.
I find the weapons room.
and I can pull the launch chip
before she can fire any of those nukes.
- That is too crazy.
- What you're saying is too dangerous.
We'll do both.
Knock. knock.
Five vehicles just breached the base.
They just don't give up. do they?
All right. let's haul ass. team.
Double time. double time.
Letty. let's roll.
Go! Go. go. go!
Change of plans. Dom.
I'm sending you new coordinates.
Head there immediately.
I'm done. I want my son.
I'll tell you when you're done.
Your team is in play.
Now. meet Rhodes
and follow my instruction.
I got you covered! Go!
Move. move!
Get out of here! Go. go. go!
Okay.
How do you like this?
Remote link has been severed.
I'll take care of this.
Hi. Ramsey.
She's regained control.
Damn it. she's good.
They're entering the weapons room.
Oh. that's cute.
Yo! Pull. pull!
Roman. Roman. we gotta find the chip.
Go!
Oh. she's slick.
You're gonna have to do better
than that. though.
Okay. now you're starting
to piss me off.
Ramsey. how much time we talking here?
You're smart...
but not smart enough.
She's locked me out.
Tej. I can't stop her.
You're gonna have to pull that chip.
I can't. This thing's gone
into attack mode.
The door's not gonna open
until you pull the chip.
Tej. we got no idea
what the hell we're looking for.
I got it.
What in the hell are you guys doing?
It wasn't me.
It-it wasn't me. okay?
It'll be labeled "guidance go."
Guidance go. guidance...
Okay. I got something.
- What?
- It says...
H-Hakslak...
s-slak-lak...
smok... belzak... marak...
Do you understand that?
Wow. nasty.
Hmm.
Quite a show.
We're arming the nuke.
Nuke's going hot. She's
trying to fire this thing.
Roger that.
We're moving out.
- Disable that chip. now!
- Roman. what are you seeing?
Come on. talk to me.
I don't see shit.
I'm holding on.
And we have a countdown.
What the hell is going on. man?
We're about to launch a nuclear missile
is what the hell is going on.
Pull the damn chip!
Countdown. Countdown!
- Look for a countdown!
- What countdown?
The missiles need to activate to launch.
The countdown timer won't be in Russian.
The countdown...
Let's show the world what we've got.
No. no. no. don't press that!
I got it.
Something's wrong.
It won't launch.
Get that sub out of there. Now!
Move your ass. Roman!
- You all right?
- There's nothing all right
about any of this!
Let's go!
What about the missiles?
We got the chip.
No nukes for her.
Hell yeah.
Let's roll.
Oh. shit!
The other way!
What?
Go the other way!
The ice.
Everybody out on the ice.
Guys. we got company.
A lot of company.
All right. team. here's the plan.
There's a sea lock
at the opening of the bay.
We get there first and close it.
we can stop the submarine
from escaping into open water
and disappearing forever.
I've got the location.
It's ten miles southwest.
Ten miles? We're not gonna
make it ten seconds!
No. no. no. no. no!
This is not good! Aah!
What's the matter. Roman?
Forgot your snow tires?
You loving that Lambo now?
Oh. sh... Oh!
All right. everyone.
We'll deal with that launch chip later.
Right now I want that sub
in deep water where no one can find it.
Find me the fastest route
out of that bay.
Copy that.
Why are they shooting at me?!
Maybe 'cause you're in
an orange Lamborghini.
I don't know.
Shut up. Tej!
Dom. do you really
want to put that car in gear?
Do it. huh?
- I didn't think so.
- They're heading for the sea lock.
They're trying to trap
the sub in the bay.
I should have taken care
of this a long time ago.
Rhodes. take his team out.
I'm on it.
Roman. get in front of me.
Okay. y'all want to play rough?
Now it's my turn.
Yeah. baby!
Guys. we got snowmobiles on the right.
They're gonna flank us!
No. they ain't.
Oh. shit!
Tej!
Roman. hold tight.
I'm on the way.
I don't want to go swimming!
No!
Really. Tej?
Oh. no. no. no. no. no. no. no. no!
Oh. shit!
Roman. grab your door.
Tej!
Grab the door. Roman!
- It's so cold!
- Shit.
Oh. shit!
Whoa!
- Whoo!
- Yeah!
What is going on?!
Roman. hang on.
Tej!
Get me off of this thing!
Come on!
All right.
I've had enough of this shit!
Number 11. my ass.
Yo. Shrinkage.
We got a sub to catch.
Get in.
What?
Depressurization alert
in the cargo hold.
Drop it to 10.000 feet.
I know how much
these people mean to you.
So I will let you pick the first target.
I don't pick a target from a mile away.
I stand face to face
and look 'em dead in the eye.
Okay.
The wife it is.
Nice plane.
I'm going to enjoy having this.
Hey. don't go getting any ideas.
You and planes
don't have a good history.
No shit.
Okay... let's go. Scarface.
These assholes
ain't gonna kill themselves.
Pull up surveillance right now.
Surprise.
You're supposed to be dead.
We have a security breach
in the cargo hold.
Take care of it now.
Jesus. Mum.
You're supposed to avoid the nerves.
Oh. shut up.
Don't be such a baby.
Get to the pilot.
He's got the second key.
- Wait for my signal.
- Give Cipher my regards.
Did Toretto hold up his end of the deal?
He gave us this little thing here.
No. no. no. no.
Don't touch.
You can track Cipher with this.
but you can't do this on your own.
It's gotta be two of you.
Fine. I've got contacts.
No. you're gonna take your brother.
- No. Damn.
- Yes.
Toretto knows where he is.
He's got this thing.
It can see everything.
It's like... it's called the
Devil's Bumhole or something.
- It's called the God's Eye.
- Yeah. well. whatever.
There's no way I'm using Owen.
all right?
He's a lost cause.
He's your brother. Decks.
He's my son.
He's our family.
And our family
don't die in bloody cages.
How can you talk like that about Owen?
I can't believe you.
You've gone and upset me.
You've really upset your mother.
Call yourself a brother?
- Look. look. come here.
- You're...
Mum. Okay. okay.
Every time.
Owen.
In position.
Go.
I'm in.
I've got the package. Toretto.
All 12 pounds of him.
Yeah!
Dada. Dada.
You made me miss my shot.
What you think you're doing?
Looking at you dead in the eye.
That was for Elena.
Rhodes.
He's no longer with us.
Rhodes picked the wrong target.
Congratulations. Dom.
You just killed your son.
You're wrong.
I just saved him.
And you just took your foot
off the tiger's neck.
All right. governor.
it's gonna get noisy.
This is for your ears.
Good?
Let's go.
No. Stop him!
Do not let him get off this plane.
We got another problem.
That truck's got enough
missiles to take us all out.
Then don't give 'em a target.
Everybody. get in front of us. line up.
- and we'll take the hit.
- What?
I need to switch cars right now.
- Roman. here comes the bad part.
- What?
Whoa!
Whoo!
Hang in there. guys.
We're almost to the lock.
It's easy for you to say
when your ass ain't on fire.
All right. little man.
This might be a little scary.
but it's gonna be a lot of fun.
Ready?
How's the music? Good?
They're locking on.
Sorry. guys. I got no tricks left.
What do we do now?
We start praying.
Hell yeah!
There's Dom.
What. is this guy on our side now?
Who the hell cares?
He just saved our ass.
Good to be riding with you again. man.
Toretto just cleared the way for them.
- Someone. give me something.
- Torpedoes are ready.
Then launch them!
Shit.
Take the wheel.
I ain't taking shit!
Take the wheel!
Where are you going?
- This is crazy!
- Speed up!
- Left and back!
- What?
Turn the goddamn wheel
to the left really quickly.
Oh. got it.
Boom. baby.
Going for a ride.
Back in a sec.
Where's that smile?
There it is.
You were gonna shoot a baby?
You sick bastard.
You're not gonna want to see this.
♪ We've been good ♪
♪ But we can't last ♪
♪ Hurry. Christmas ♪
♪ Hurry fast... ♪
Is that you or him?
Him. Good.
The torpedoes missed.
They're gonna reach the lock
before the sub does.
The hell they are.
Get ready for this.
Oh. shit!
We're gonna need a bigger truck.
It's right under us.
Get out the way!
I'm not going back in that water!
Get us out of here!
Why are you always yelling?
- This bitch is crazy.
- Look out!
Yeah. that's not good.
That's not good.
Please tell me there's
nothing to worry about.
Relax. We got this.
That's my girl.
The sub's too close. We ain't
making it to the gate in time.
We're just gonna let it get away?
Not if I know Dom.
You lose. Dom.
I destroyed two of your teams.
I killed your redheaded boyfriend.
and I put two killers
on your untraceable plane.
You lost the minute
you interrupted my honeymoon.
Now guess who I'm coming for.
Put a heat-seeker on him now.
Now!
Fire!
That's a goddamn heat-seeker
coming at us!
Peel off!
Head to the shore!
All right.
Come and get it.
No. no. no. no. no.
No. no.
Dive! Dive!
This...
This is for my son.
Dom!
You're out of bullets. Deckard.
Not like I'm gonna need a gun
to take care of you.
How did you find me?
You want to see the old Dom?
Watch.
Resourceful.
You have a lot to answer for. Cipher.
What you put my family through.
My mother.
I'm gonna make sure
that never happens again.
To anyone.
There is only one flaw in your plan.
What's that?
Only one of us has a parachute.
Told you this would be fun.
Time to land. boys.
You know I never left you. Letty.
I know.
And you know I never will.
I have so much to tell you.
Yeah. you do.
And you can start with that bitch.
Now. that's Dominic Toretto.
Hey. Dom.
I'm just throwing it out there.
We need to get up out of here
'cause there's all kind of nuclearism
- happening under this ice.
- Relax.
Without the trigger chips.
those nukes are harmless.
Okay. so we good. then.
Let me go and get
my young selfie levels up.
You realize this is classified. right?
Not today.
Unbelievable.
All right. can we
get up out of here now?
I'm freezing.
♪ It doesn't get much better than this ♪
♪ Spent too much time
getting ready for this ♪
♪ These days it seems
like I just can't miss ♪
♪ And I must confess... ♪
It's okay.
Don't worry.
He's gonna be here soon.
I get it.
Y'all got a lot in common.
Computer hacks. God's Eye.
geeks. nerd. the... You know.
But we got a lot in common. too. right?
- Like what?
- We walk in the room.
and we're oozing sex appeal.
We steal the show.
Me and you. hip to hip.
is a problem. That's us.
I'm asking a real question right now.
Is it gonna be Revenge of the Nerds...
Or...
The Dark Knight? Huh?
To be honest. I like both of you.
Yeah. baby.
You know what I mean?
All right. all right. baby...
But just before we get into all of that.
let me ask you one question.
You can ask me anything.
Anything.
What's my last name?
When you guys figure it out. then...
- I guess you can let me know.
- It's gonna be Parker.
That's... that's all
that really matters.
- Jones. Uh...
- Mrs. Parker.
- Right?
- Hey. Mrs. Parker.
- Hey.
- Letty.
I wanted to thank you.
No need.
Cipher is still on the loose.
There's been some reports
she's in Athens.
but matter of time before we find her.
thanks to you guys.
So. I got you a party favor.
This can't be good.
Your record's been cleared.
Full reinstatement.
You got your job back.
That is. if you want it.
- If I want.
- Mm-hmm.
You know. after 16 years.
I figure it's time for a little break.
Wow.
Daddy's staying home.
Mmm... mwah.
Nobody.
Keep in touch.
Ah. hang on a second.
This could be interesting.
What made you think I'd do it?
Brotherhood.
I saw that look you gave Cipher.
Knew you wanted revenge.
Glad I did it.
Can't believe you went to see my mother.
Hey.
Hey. you know my son
is only American muscle.
Hey. look. had to give him something.
Look how I tested the little guy.
Come on. Roman.
Get to cooking. buddy.
We all love you.
Come on. now.
All this fuss over you.
Yes.
Elena. I promise to keep our son safe.
And now he always will be.
I want to introduce you
to the most important person
in my universe.
One who never gave up on me.
He's beautiful.
You've heard me say
that you never turn your back on family.
And I want to thank you all
for never turning your back on me.
You want to meet them?
All right.
Everyone...
meet Brian.
- Oh. man.
- Yes. Yeah!
I love it.
- Go. Brian.
- That's right.
Welcome to the family. Brian.
Okay. I guess it's my turn to say grace.
We thank you for giving us family.
We sit here in praise.
Thank you for giving us the strength...
♪ Raise a cup up for all my day ones ♪
♪ Two middle fingers for the haters ♪
♪ Life's only getting greater ♪
♪ Straight up from nothing we go ♪
♪ Higher than the highest skyscraper ♪
♪ No Little League. we major ♪
♪ The proof is in the paper ♪
♪ We put the good in the.
good in the good life ♪
♪ We put the good in the ♪
♪ Good in the good life ♪
♪ We put the bad in the past.
now we all right ♪
- ♪ Hey. hey. hey. hey. hey ♪
- ♪ Kehlani. I got you. yeah ♪
♪ And it's a feeling
that I can't explain ♪
♪ How you make it and your team
still stay the same ♪
♪ Stay down from the jump
and they never change ♪
♪ Man. this a moment
I could never trade. yeah ♪
♪ I put my team in position.
now they making a killing ♪
♪ Stacking blue faces
straight to the ceiling ♪
♪ Out in Vegas I'm with 'em ♪
♪ Ordering bottles of that Ace
when they sit 'em ♪
♪ Till there ain't enough space
up on the table to fit 'em ♪
- ♪ Go ahead and ♪
- ♪ Raise a cup up ♪
♪ For all my day ones ♪
♪ Two middle fingers for the haters ♪
♪ Life's only getting greater ♪
♪ Straight up from nothing we go ♪
♪ Higher than the highest skyscraper ♪
♪ No Little League. we major ♪
♪ The proof is in the paper ♪
♪ We put the good in the.
good in the good life ♪
- ♪ The good life ♪
- ♪ We put the good in the ♪
♪ Good in the good life ♪
♪ We put the bad in the past.
now we all right ♪
- ♪ Hey. hey. hey. hey ♪
- ♪ Yeah. yeah. yeah ♪
♪ You know. uh ♪
♪ We put the good in the.
good in the good life ♪
- ♪ The good life ♪
- ♪ We put the good in the ♪
- ♪ Good in the good life ♪
- ♪ I said the good life ♪
♪ We put the bad in the past ♪
- ♪ Now we all right ♪
- ♪ We all right ♪
- ♪ Yeah. yeah. yeah. yeah ♪
- ♪ Hey. hey. hey. hey. hey. ♪
♪ Yeah. yeah. yeah ♪
- ♪ Yeah. yeah. yeah ♪
- ♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Yeah. yeah. yeah ♪
♪ One more ride. one more race ♪
♪ We go all out. we don't play ♪
♪ We don't slow down. ain't no brakes ♪
♪ I'm-a go off. I'm-a ride tonight ♪
♪ It don't matter what we face ♪
♪ I'm the master of my fate ♪
♪ I'm-a go off. I'm-a go off ♪
♪ I'm-a go off. I'm-a go off.
yeah. I gotta go now ♪
♪ Taking off and I'm riding
on the road now ♪
♪ Hit the gas. no brakes. gotta go now ♪
♪ Put my life on the line.
yeah. it's on me ♪
♪ Blood rushing
through my veins. no I.V. ♪
♪ Ride. switching lanes.
you can't stop me ♪
♪ You can smell the propane
when you pass me ♪
- ♪ Propane ♪
- ♪ Ride for the gang ♪
- ♪ Because I'm the chief ♪
- ♪ Gang. gang ♪
♪ Helicopter hovering. it's high speed ♪
♪ Chase. drive straight ♪
♪ I'm-a race to the cake ♪
♪ Flame on it. no chain on me ♪
♪ All of us became homies ♪
♪ One more ride. one more race ♪
♪ We go all out. we don't play ♪
♪ We don't slow down. ain't no brakes ♪
♪ I'm-a go off. I'm-a ride tonight ♪
♪ It don't matter what we face ♪
♪ I'm the master of my fate ♪
♪ I'm-a go off. I'm-a go off ♪
♪ I'm-a go off. I'm-a go off.
yeah. I gotta go now ♪
♪ Nine-nine. nine-nine ♪
♪ You're rocking with the ether child ♪
♪ In overdrive. yeah yeah ♪
♪ I-5 to I-9 ♪
- ♪ We go all night ♪
♪ Double-O speed. double-O Chevy ♪
♪ I hit the fourth gear.
hope I don't drift ♪
♪ Souped up cars all around me ♪
♪ Hot-boxing at a high speed ♪
♪ One lane driving ♪
♪ Bad thing beside me ♪
- ♪ One more time on the road ♪
- ♪ It's lit ♪
♪ One more time 'fore we go ♪
♪ One more ride. one more race ♪
♪ We go all out. we don't play ♪
♪ We don't slow down. ain't no brakes ♪
♪ I'm-a go off. I'm-a ride tonight ♪
♪ It don't matter what we face ♪
♪ I'm the master of my fate ♪
♪ I'm-a go off. I'm-a go off ♪
♪ I'm-a go off. I'm-a go off.
yeah. I gotta go now ♪
♪ Gotta go now. gotta go ♪
♪ Swerving in my whip. can't slow down ♪
♪ Driving fancy cars.
boy. I'm on the road now ♪
♪ Automatic start.
my Vic take a code now ♪
♪ Yeah. rock star.
heavy metal. no guitar ♪
♪ Why you pay so much for your Nissan? ♪
♪ Because it's GTR ♪
♪ First I shift it. click it ♪
♪ Burning rubber like I'm moving dark ♪
♪ Drive at night. I chop my top ♪
♪ So I can relate to the stars ♪
♪ Yeah. relate to the stars.
to the stars ♪
♪ I'm-a race you for a pink slip ♪
♪ I got nitrous in my car
so tell me what you thinking ♪
♪ My adrenaline start pumping
so I best stop blinking ♪
♪ One more ride. one more race ♪
♪ We go all out. we don't play ♪
♪ We don't slow down. ain't no brakes ♪
♪ I'm-a go off. I'm-a ride tonight ♪
♪ It don't matter what we face ♪
♪ I'm-a go off. I'm-a go off ♪
♪ I'm-a go off. I'm-a go off.
I gotta go now. ♪
♪ DJ Chose ♪
♪ Oh. yeah ♪
♪ Yeah. yeah. yeah ♪
♪ Yeah. yeah ♪
♪ All these horses in my car
got me going fast ♪
♪ I just want to do the dash.
put my pedal to the gas ♪
♪ Going so fast. hope I don't crash ♪
♪ One false move.
that could be my last ♪
♪ All these horses in my car
got me going fast ♪
♪ I just want to do the dash.
put my pedal to the gas ♪
♪ Going so fast. hope I don't crash ♪
♪ One false move.
that could be my last ♪
♪ I just rolled up in the Benz ♪
♪ It was just me and my mans ♪
♪ Fishbowl no tint ♪
♪ Scooping your... and her friends ♪
♪ Wanna take that... to the movies ♪
♪ Ain't got no love for the groupies ♪
♪ Seat back while she do me ♪
♪ She get wetter than Jacuzzis ♪
♪ She don't go like a green light ♪
♪ She get ran through like a red light ♪
♪ If the... right then the bread right ♪
♪ Shorty know I'll be there
every night ♪
♪ Problem. problem. what they
want like steak sauce ♪
♪ Zero to 60. I take off ♪
♪ Can't see me.
looking like Ray Charles ♪
♪ They tell me slow down.
I'm going too fast ♪
♪ Young... I just wanna do the dash ♪
♪ I'm so reckless. hope I don't crash ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm ballin'.
like the whip stolen ♪
♪ Yeah. all these horses
in my car got me going fast ♪
♪ I just want to do the dash.
put my pedal to the gas ♪
♪ Going so fast. hope I don't crash ♪
♪ One false move.
that could be my last ♪
♪ All big bankrolls ♪
♪ I got no ♪
♪ I just left my girlfriend ♪
♪ I'm in love with the ghost now ♪
♪ She's full of emotions ♪
♪ And now she's my old ♪
♪ 'Cause my 'Rari knows how
to roll when it goes down ♪
♪ And my watch on froze ♪
♪ Watch it glow with the lights out ♪
♪ If it's hot or cold. we gonna
still bring the bikes out ♪
♪ I just bought a Rolls-Royce
and I hop in a Lamb' now ♪
♪ When I push the button ♪
♪ They like.
"What the... is that sound?" ♪
♪ All these horses in my car
got me going fast ♪
♪ I just want to do the dash.
put my pedal to the gas ♪
♪ Going so fast. hope I don't crash ♪
♪ One false move.
that could be my last ♪
♪ All these horses in my car
got me going fast ♪
♪ I just want to do the dash.
put my pedal to the gas ♪
♪ Going so fast. hope I don't crash ♪
♪ One false move.
that could be my last ♪
♪ Yo. ♪
♪ Yo. play. play. play. play ♪
♪ Play. he gonna get his head bust ♪
♪ You know how we comin' ♪
♪ Strapped like the Navy SEALs ♪
♪ Promise you don't want it ♪
♪ This for them. this for them ♪
♪ Be speaking on me ♪
♪ Rob who? You got me... up ♪
♪ You ain't takin' nothin' ♪
♪ It gonna. it gonna be a murder ♪
♪ Play with that money ♪
♪ It's gonna. it's gonna be a murder ♪
♪ Come run up on me ♪
♪ Be a. it's gonna be a murder ♪
♪ Burn you and your homie ♪
♪ It's gonna. it's gonna be a murder ♪
♪ Thinkin' that I'm stuntin' ♪
♪ It's gonna be a murder.
gonna be a murder ♪
♪ If you thinkin' 'bout takin'
somethin' from me ♪
♪ Talk about your body ♪
♪ But I bet you ain't
gonna play with me ♪
♪ Try me if you wanna ♪
♪ I stay with that burner on me ♪
♪ What you doin'? ♪
♪ I can't let you get no rip off me ♪
♪ Must think I'm a... ♪
♪ I don't know who the...
he must take me for ♪
♪ That... that you talkin'
ain't fearin' us ♪
♪ How you come. you ain't seein' us ♪
♪ Say we beefin'. gonna
catch him and wet him up ♪
♪ Tell. tell me pull up
and I'm pullin' up ♪
♪ Up. let it bang.
we ain't sparin' nothin' ♪
♪ Caught him up in the bottom.
he ran from me ♪
♪ So you know we flexin'
with them bands ♪
♪ Whole lotta more up in my pants ♪
♪ Try to take it. all you hear is bang ♪
♪ Play. he gonna get his head bust ♪
♪ You know how we comin' ♪
♪ Strapped like the Navy SEALs ♪
♪ Promise you don't want it ♪
♪ This for them. this for them ♪
♪ Be speaking on me ♪
♪ Rob who? You got me... up ♪
♪ You ain't takin' nothin' ♪
♪ It gonna. it gonna be a murder ♪
♪ Play with that money ♪
♪ It's gonna. it's gonna be a murder ♪
♪ Come run up on me ♪
♪ Be a. it's gonna be a murder ♪
♪ Burn you and your homie ♪
♪ It's gonna. it's gonna be a murder ♪
♪ Thinkin' that I'm stuntin' ♪
♪ It's gonna be a murder. be a murder ♪
♪ Be a murder. be a murder.
be a murder... ♪
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm